

ÖZGE AHRAS

Frontend Developer

Frontend Developer, working in an agile team with 3 years of experience, developing with Javascript, HTML/CSS, angularjs in the IT industry. Enthusiastic about learning new technologies. Training ReactJS. You can reach my projects on github.com/ozgeahras

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering - Bachelor's Degree

Mustafa Kemal University | 2008– 2012

LANGUAGE

Native Turkish

Advanced English

- <u>ozgeahras@gmail.com</u>
- ozgeahras.com
- github.com/ozgeahras
- ☐ linkedin.com/in/ozgeahras
- 💡 Istanbul/ Turkey

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Yapı Kredi Technology | 2020 - Now

- Developing and maintaining product with java and Angularjs using RESTful APIs.
- Using GIT and Bitbucket for versioning.
- Working in an agile environment.

Software Developer(ITSM Consultant)

ODYA & BT Bilgi & Yapı Kredi | 2012 - 2020

- Created backend processes using automation and workflow third-party tools with pure Javascript, HTML/CSS, powershell, SQL, SOAP/REST API
- Created frontend forms with third-party tools for customers
- Maintained third-party tools, created reports, analyzed customer's need and developed workflows.

SKILLS

- Javascript ES6+
- HTML/CSS
- GIT
- AngularJS
- ReactJS (self-taught)
- RESTful Webservices
- Bootstrap
- SQL

CERTIFICATIONS

- Responsive Web Design | freeCodeCamp.org
- The Frontend Developer Career Path | scrimba.com
- From Zero to Advanced Modern Javascript Lessons ES7+ - 2020 | Udemy.com